And what else do we also have gems over here?
So if I click on "explore gems", we'll see that.
Yeah, GemManager, Discover, create and manage gems.
Gems are custom versions of Gemini that give you tailored responses over here.
We can create a special model and we can train some kind of a special part of the AI
to do a very specific thing for us.
So we don't want to go through that for now,
but that's all that we have with Gemini for now.
We also can search, so by clicking on this option,
we'll be able to search among all the chat history that we've had with Gemini.
And that's all with these Google's AI tool,
AI Chatbot, that is very trending these days.
And we hear a lot about.